National Organization for Women, New York State Chapter; Records apap029
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- President's Subject Files, 1968-1988; 2; 12 cubic ft.
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: Bias Bill (Howard Beach), 1987-1988 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: Civil Rights Bill, 1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: Employment Contract--Joan Butcher, 1984 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: Foster Care, 1985 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: Fundraising, 1984; 1986-1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: Hate Crimes Statistics Bill, 1988 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: Housing, 1985 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: Lobbying, 1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: Lobbyist Reports, 1986 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: Local Ordinances, 1984; 1986 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: NOW Job Descriptions, 1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: NYC Executive Order #22, 1984 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: Special Project Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: Staff Reports, Memos, etc, 1985 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Lesbian & Gay Rights: Target State Proposal, National NOW & Veatch Program, 1985-1986 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Lobbyists' Reports, 1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Long Island NOW - Nassau, Inc., 1980; 1987; 1991-1992 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Long Island Women's Coalition, 1983-1984 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Maternity Health Act, 1988 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Mid-Suffolk NOW, 1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Midwives, 1986 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Monroe-Woodbury Bus Drivers, 1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Mutual Orders of Protection Project, 1988 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - National Coalition of American Nuns, 1985 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - National March for Women's Lives, 1986 March 9 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - NOW National Conference, 1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - NOW New York City Chapter, 1984 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - NOW-NYS--Centralized Dues Collection, 1979; 1981-1982 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - NOW-NYS Chapter Renewal Monetary Report, 1982-1984; 1988 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - NOW-NYS Convention, 1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - NOW-NYS--Gotham Chapter, 1987-1988 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - NOW-NYS International Feminist Study Tour--Mexico, 1987 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - NOW-NYS--National Central Dues Projections, 1980-1981 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - NOW-NYS PAC, 1985 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - NOW-NYS State Conference, 1985 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - New York State and National NOW Membership Surveys, 1984-1985 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - New York Temporary State Commission on Lobbying, 1982-1983 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Northern Chautauqua County NOW Chapter, 1986 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission: Reform Proposal, 1984-1985 (Box 9 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Parental Leave, 1986-1987 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Park Project, Inc, (Hiring Practices of Palisades Interstate Park Commission), 1985 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Paul, Rosina (Haitian Refugee), 1984 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Pay Equity--NYC, 1987 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Pay Equity--State, 1987 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Pay Equity Rally, 1985 August 26 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Phelps Dodge--Arizona Copper Strike, 1985 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Political Action Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Political Action Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Political Action Committee--State Coordinators, 1986 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Political Action Information, 1985 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Political Endorsements, 1988 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Postal Rate, 1984-1987 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Presidential Campaign, 1988 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Regents, 1988 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Reproductive Rights, 1984-1988 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Rollova, Marta, 1988 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - St Patrick's Day Stag Dinner, 1987 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Schroeder, Congresswomen Pat, Presidential Campaign, 1987 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1987 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Speakers' Bureau, 1985 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Staff, 1985 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Suffolk Court House, 1986 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - "Surrogate" Parenting, 1987-1988 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Tag Day (Fundraising), 1986 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Task Force Chairs, 1985 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Task Force on Pornography, Sexual Assault & Battering--Folder 1, 1986-1988 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Task Force on Pornography, Sexual Assault & Battering--Folder 2, 1987-1988 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Task Force on Pornography, Sexual Assault & Battering--Folder 3, 1986-1988 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Task Force on Pornography, Sexual Assault & Battering--Folder 4, 1986-1988 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Task Force on Pornography, Sexual Assault & Battering--Folder 5, 1986-1988 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Task Force on Pornography, Sexual Assault & Battering--Folder 6, 1984-1986 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Task Force on Pornography, Sexual Assault & Battering--Folder 7, 1983-1985 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Task Force on Pornography, Sexual Assault & Battering--Folder 8, 1985-1988 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Task Force to Encourage Electoral Participation, 1987 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Tax Proposals, 1987 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Ulster NOW chapter, 1987 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - United Nations Conference on Disarmament and Development, 1987 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - University NOW, 1984 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Veterans--Partridge, Jacquelyn A, 1986 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Westchester NOW Chapter, 1987 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - "What Now" Forum (with two cassettes), 1984 December 3 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Women in the Courts, 1986-1987 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Women in the Courts II, 1988 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1985 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Workmen's Compensation Set-aside, 1978-1979; 1986-1988 (Box 10 (2-President's Subject Files), Folder 46)
- Issues Files, 1966-1985; 3; 5 cubic ft.
  The NOW-NYS Issues series contains journal articles, newspaper clippings, feminist literature and bibliographies, legislative and task force memoranda, committee and research reports, newsletters, leaflets and fliers of other feminist organizations, feminist art, correspondence with NOW-NYS presidents, testimony at public hearings and legal proceedings, posters and announcements of events, state and federal laws and proposed bills relating to discrimination and gender bias in education (1972-1982), labor (1970-1982), and politics (1973-1985), abortion (1970-1985), women's health care (1973-1981) and birth control issues (1973-1982), domestic relations (1981-1985), older women and aging (1971-1983), the Equal Rights Amendment (1971-1982), lesbian and gay rights (1987-1981), and the women's movement in general (1971-1985).
  - Abortion--Law and legislation, 1970-1982 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 1)
  - Abortion--Moral and religious aspects, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 2)
  - Abortion--Personal narratives, 1975-1981 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 3)
  - Abortion--Pro-Choice Movement, 1972-1977 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 4)
  - Abortion--Pro-Choice Movement, 1978-1985 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 5)
  - Abortion--Pro-Life Movement, 1971-1982 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 6)
  - Abortion in the press, 1971-1985 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 7)
  - Abused women, 1975-1985 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 8)
  - Abzug, Bella (b.1920- ), 1972-1976 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 9)
  - Adoption and foster care, 1972-1976 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 10)
  - Affirmative Action Programs, 1970-1973 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 11)
  - Affirmative Action Programs, 1974-1982 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 12)
  - Aged women, 1971-1976 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 13)
  - Aged women, 1978-1983 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 14)
  - Alcoholism, 1975-1979 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 15)
  - Assertiveness training, 1972-1985 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 16)
  - Birth control, 1973-1982 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 17)
  - Birth control--Population control, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 18)
  - Birth control--Sterilization, 1974-1981 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 19)
  - Child abuse, 1975-1980 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 20)
  - Childbirth, 1975-1977 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 21)
  - Child care, 1970-1982 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 22)
  - Civil rights, 1974-1981 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 23)
  - Comic books, strips, 1970-1978 (Box 1 (3-Issues Files), Folder 24)
  - Computers, 1981; 1984 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 1)
  - Cuomo, Mario (b.1932- ), 1982 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 2)
  - Continuing education, 1961-1982 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 3)
  - Discrimination in education, 1963-1972 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 4)
  - Discrimination in education, 1973 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 5)
  - Discrimination in education, 1974 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 6)
  - Discrimination in education, 1975-1979 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 7)
  - Discrimination in education, 1980-1985 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 8)
  - Discrimination in education--By states, 1972-1981 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 9)
  - Discrimination in education--Occupational training, 1964-1984 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 10)
  - Discrimination in education--Occupational training (bound publications), 1980-1981 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 11)
  - Discrimination in education--Occupational training (position papers), 1981-1982 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 12)
  - Discrimination in education--Title IX, 1972-1982 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 13)
  - Discrimination in education--Title XX, 1975 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 14)
  - Discrimination in education--Textbook bias, 1965-1973 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 15)
  - Discrimination in education--Textbook bias, 1974-1982 (Box 2 (3-Issues Files), Folder 16)
  - Discrimination in employment, 1963-1969 (Box 3 (3-Issues Files), Folder 1)
  - Discrimination in employment, 1970-1971 (Box 3 (3-Issues Files), Folder 2)
  - Discrimination in employment, 1972 (Box 3 (3-Issues Files), Folder 3)
  - Discrimination in employment, 1973-1975 (Box 3 (3-Issues Files), Folder 4)
  - Discrimination in employment, 1976-1981 (Box 3 (3-Issues Files), Folder 5)
  - Discrimination in higher education, 1970-1976 (Box 3 (3-Issues Files), Folder 6)
  - Discrimination in higher education, 1977-1982 (Box 3 (3-Issues Files), Folder 7)
  - Divorce, 1970-1985 (Box 3 (3-Issues Files), Folder 8)
  - Divorce--Child support--Child custody, 1971-1985 (Box 3 (3-Issues Files), Folder 9)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1971-1976 (Box 3 (3-Issues Files), Folder 10)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1977-1982 (Box 3 (3-Issues Files), Folder 11)
  - Euthanasia (right to die), 1973-1976 (Box 3 (3-Issues Files), Folder 12)
  - Family, 1977-1980 (Box 3 (3-Issues Files), Folder 13)
  - Family violence, 1976-1985 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 1)
  - Feminists, 1970-1982 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 2)
  - Feminist literature, 1970-1971 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 3)
  - Feminist literature, 1972-1982 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 4)
  - Feminist literature--bibliographies, 1970-1981 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 5)
  - Genetics, 1972-1977 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 6)
  - Handicapped, 1971-1978 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 7)
  - Hearst, Patty (b.1954- ), 1971-1976 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 8)
  - Housewives, 1971-1981 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 9)
  - International Women's Year 1975, 1974-1976 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 10)
  - Labor movement, 1970-1982 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 11)
  - Lesbianism, 1970-1981 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, 1972-1982 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 13)
  - MS Magazine, 1971-1974 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 14)
  - New York State Education Department--Press releases, 1980 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 15)
  - Nursing--Study and teaching, 1977-1979 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 16)
  - Politics, 1973-1985 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 17)
  - Prostitution, 1971-1979 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 18)
  - Rape, 1971-1975 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 19)
  - Rape, 1976-1981 (Box 4 (3-Issues Files), Folder 20)
  - Sex discrimination against women, 1971-1977 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 1)
  - Sexism in language, 1970-1979 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 2)
  - Teenage pregnancy--teenage sex, 1975-1978 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 3)
  - Toys--toymaking, 1971-1974 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 4)
  - Witchcraft, 1974 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 5)
  - Women--Health care, 1973-1981 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 6)
  - Women--History, 1969-1985 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 7)
  - Women--Mental health, 1970-1980 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 8)
  - Women--Pensions and insurance, 1963-1976 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 9)
  - Women authors, 1970-1982 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 10)
  - Women comedians, 1973-1976 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 11)
  - Women consultants, 1974-1976 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 12)
  - Women musicians, 1975-1983 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 13)
  - Women and religion, 1976-1979 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 14)
  - Women as consumers, 1972-1976 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 15)
  - Women in film, 1971-1982 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 16)
  - Women in literature, 1972-1981 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 17)
  - Women in mass media, 1969-1979 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 18)
  - Women in politics, 1973-1979 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 19)
  - Women in politics, 1980-1985 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 20)
  - Women in sports, 1974-1979 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 21)
  - Women in television, 1970-1979 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 22)
  - Women in the theatre, 1972-1976 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 23)
  - Women's centers, 1971-1982 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 24)
  - Women's Liberation Movement, 1971-1985 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 25)
  - Women's sexual behavior, 1972-1978 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 26)
  - Working women, 1966-1973 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 27)
  - Working women, 1974-1982 (Box 5 (3-Issues Files), Folder 28)
- Lobbyist Files, 1972-1988; 4; 2.7 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject for a specific year or group of years.
  The NOW-NYS Lobbyists' files contain correspondence, lobbyists' notes on contacts with politicians and other lobbying groups, testimony, depositions from public hearings, bill proposals, and memoranda relating to the women's liberation movement in New York. Issues covered include NOW-NYS's responses to legislative bills concerning employment, abortion, child abuse, domestic violence, gay and lesbian rights, marriage and divorce, rape prevention, reproductive rights, and sex equity in education. Correspondents include the lobbyists and NOW-NYS presidents, and Barbara T Rochman, the NOW-NYS V.P. for lobbying 1984-1988.
  - Voting records, 1972-1975 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 1)
  - Abortion, 1977-1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 3)
  - Education, 1977-1979 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 4)
  - Education: Title IX, 1975 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 5)
  - Employment, 1976-1978 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 6)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1974-1983 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 7)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, Undated (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 8)
  - ERA Assembly debate, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 9)
  - Family Court & Domestic Relations, 1976-1979 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 10)
  - "The Good Guys & Gals": Legislative Representatives for Social Concerns, 1978-1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 11)
  - Health & Social Services, 1975-1978 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 12)
  - Higher education, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 13)
  - Human Rights, 1977 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 14)
  - Legislative Newsletter, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 15)
  - Legislative Program, 1978 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 16)
  - Legislative Program, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 17)
  - Legislative survey, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 18)
  - Legislators & Chapters, Undated (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 19)
  - Lobby Day, 1979 March 13 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 20)
  - Marriage, 1976-1979 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 21)
  - Memoranda, 1975; 1979 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 22)
  - Municipal Services, 1976-1978 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 23)
  - Nolan, Howard C.: NYS Senator, 42nd District, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 24)
  - NOW-NYS Lobbyist, 1978 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 25)
  - Padavan, Frank: NYS Senator, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 26)
  - Rape, Undated (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 27)
  - Sex discrimination, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 28)
  - Sports, 1977 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 29)
  - Stratton, Samuel S.: NYS Congress, 28th District, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 30)
  - Assembly, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 31)
  - Bills, miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 32)
  - Community Outreach Program, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 33)
  - Daily notes, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 34)
  - Education, 1981-1982 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 35)
  - Employment, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 36)
  - Employment Task Force, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 37)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 38)
  - ERA Impact Clearinghouse, 1981-1983 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 39)
  - Finance Vice-President: mailing, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 40)
  - Forms, 1980 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 41)
  - Important votes, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 42)
  - Indecent materials to minors, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 43)
  - Joint Custody, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 44)
  - Legislative memos sent to Senate or Assembly, 1981-1982 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 45)
  - Legislative Program, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 46)
  - Lesbian rights, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 47)
  - Lobby Day, 1981 March 24 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 48)
  - Lobbyist introductory letter, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 49)
  - Lobbyist reports, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 50)
  - Marriage & divorce, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 51)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 52)
  - Moynihan, Daniel: United States Senate, NYS, 1981 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 53)
  - No-fault divorce, 1981 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 54)
  - Public assistance, 1980 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 55)
  - Rape Prevention & Control Program, 1981 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 56)
  - Reproductive rights, 1981 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 57)
  - Russell, Susan: NOW-NYS Lobbyist, 1981 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 58)
  - Special Session, 1980 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 59)
  - Voting record: NYS Assembly, 1980 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 60)
  - Women's Study Group, 1981 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 61)
  - Data files on NYS Assembly: A-K, Undated (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 62)
  - Data files on NYS Assembly: L-Z, Undated (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 63)
  - Data files on NYS Senate: A-L, Undated (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 64)
  - Data files on NYS Senate: M-Z, Undated (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 65)
  - Education: NOW Bill, 1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 66)
  - Education: Statewide Advisory Council on Equal Opportunity for Women, 1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 67)
  - Equal rights Amendment, 1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 68)
  - Legislative memos sent to Assembly or Senate, 1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 69)
  - Legislative Program, 1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 70)
  - Lobby Day, 1982 March 23 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 71)
  - NOW-NYS budget, 1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 72)
  - NOW-NYS Convention, 1982 April 2-1982 April 4 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 73)
  - Voting records, 1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 74)
  - 25-Age of support, A5906, 02/16/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 75)
  - 28-Long Shore Workers, S4062A, A6876A, 02/22/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 76)
  - 29-Sex discrimination, 2827, A3726, 02/26/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 77)
  - 32-Child support, A3215, A5033, 03/08/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 78)
  - 33-Child protection, 539, S364, 03/08/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 79)
  - 34-Child support, S7901, A8857A, 03/10/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 80)
  - 35-Employment, mailings, 03/06/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 81)
  - 36-Alimony, A10085, 03/10/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 82)
  - 37-Personal Property Law, 6292B, 03/09/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 83)
  - 38-Alimony, S7901, 03/11/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 84)
  - 39-Sex discrimination, A3726, 03/11/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 85)
  - 40-Task forces, mailings, memoranda, kills, 03/09/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 86)
  - 42-Marriage, A1502, 03/15/1982 (Box 2 (4-Lobbyist Files), Folder 87)